在离密尔沃基不远的森林保护区
discovered 3 partially buried bodies
发现了三具被部分掩埋的尸体
in a forest preserve just outside Milwaukee.
两男一女
Two male and one female.
看来嫌犯并没有性别偏好
He doesn't appear to have a gender preference.
尸体已经腐烂  他们不是同时被杀的
Decomposed. They weren't all killed at the same time.
不愧我叫你鹰眼
And that is why I call you eagle eye.
初步法医报告显示
Preliminary M.E. reports
每名死者被杀的时间间隔约为一个月
they'd each been killed about a month apart.
最新的死者  苏珊·克拉克
The most recent victim, Susan Clark,
死于大概两周前
has been dead approximately two weeks.
28岁的外国舞女和妓女
28-year-old exotic dancer and prostitute.
高危险生活方式  其他两名死者呢
High-risk lifestyle. What about the other two?
我还没查出他们的身份
I haven't I.D.'d them yet.
死因呢
'Cause of death?
也还在调查中
Still working on that, too.
他们身上都是咬痕
Looks like they were all covered in bite marks.
嫌犯咬的吗
From the unsub?
可能是森林里的动物咬的
Probably from critters out in the woods.